module.exports=[
    {
        "question":"  Which of the following statement is valid to use a Node module http in a Node based application?",
        "option1":"var http = require('http');",
        "option2":"var http = import('http');",
        "option3":" package http;",
        "option4":"import http;",
        "correctans":1,
    },
    {
        "question":" Which of the following command will show all the modules installed locally.",
        "option1":"$ npm ls -g",
        "option2":"$ npm ls",
        "option3":"$ node ls -g",
        "option4":" $ node ls",
        "correctans":2,
    },
    {
        "question":" Which of the following is true about readable stream?",
        "option1":"Readable stream is used for read operation.",
        "option2":" Output of readable stream can be input to a writable stream.",
        "option3":" Both of the above.",
        "option4":"None of the above.",
        "correctans":3,
    },
    {
        "question":" Which of the following is true about fs module of Node? ",
        "option1":"Every method in fs module have synchronous as well as asynchronous form.",
        "option2":"Asynchronous methods of fs module take last parameter as completion function callback and first parameter of the callback function as error.",
        "option3":" Both of the above.",
        "option4":"None of the above",
        "correctans":3,
    },
    {
        "question":" Which of the following is true about setInterval(cb, ms) global function? ",
        "option1":" The setInterval(cb, ms) global function is used to run callback cb repeatedly after at least ms milliseconds.",
        "option2":"The setInterval(cb, ms) method returns an opaque value that represents the timer which can be used to clear the timer using the function clearInterval(t).",
        "option3":"Both of the above",
        "option4":"None of  the above",
        "correctans":3,
    }, {
        "question":"Which of the following code prints current directory? ",
        "option1":"console.log('Current directory: ' + process.cwd());",
        "option2":"console.log('Current directory: ' + console.cwd());",
        "option3":"console.log('Current directory: ' + process.currenWorkingDirectory());",
        "option4":"None of the above",
        "correctans":1,
    },
    {
        "question":" Which of the following module is required for path specific operations? ",
        "option1":"os module",
        "option2":"fs module",
        "option3":"path module",
        "option4":"None of the above.",
        "correctans":3,
    },
    {
        "question":" Which of the following code can create a web server? ",
        "option1":"http.createServer(callback)",
        "option2":"http.createWebServer(callback)",
        "option3":" http.createHTTPServer(callback)",
        "option4":"None of the above.",
        "correctans":1,
    },
    {
        "question":" Which of the following is not a valid HTTP method? ",
        "option1":"get",
        "option2":"put",
        "option3":"post",
        "option4":"header",
        "correctans":4,
    },
    {
        "question":"Node.js is written in _____________ .",
        "option1":"Javascript",
        "option2":"C",
        "option3":"C++",
        "option4":"All of the Above",
        "correctans":4,
    },
]